A Finding Aid to the Susan Conway Gallery Records, circa 1928, circa 1940s-2003, bulk 1987-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.susacong
Archives of American Art
- Records Regarding Patrick Oliphant, 1976-2003; Series 4; 11.5 Linear feet Boxes 11-22, 26, OV 27
  - General Files, 1978-2003; 4.1
    - Writings, Bellows ( Washington Star), 2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Yolla Bolly Press, James Robinson, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Restricted Folder (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Oversized, Signature, circa early 1990s (Box OV 27)
      Oversized material from Box 14, Folder 21
  - Exhibition and Loan Files, 1987-2003; 4.2
    Folders may contain information about multiple exhibitions/loans/gifts, and may overlap with materials in subseries 4.1.
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title, typically the exhibition title or the exhibiting institution’s name.
    - "An Art Evening to Honor Pat Oliphant," The Lotos Club (May 13, 1992), 1987; 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - ArtChicago 2002, Sculpture, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Australia, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Australian Embassy, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Australian Embassy, Exhibition (June 22 - Aug. 10, 1995), 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
    - Australian Embassy, Loans, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Bohemian Club, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Bonn, Germany, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
    - Bronze Sculpture Exhibition, Susan Conway Gallery (Mar. 18-25, 1998) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Campaign Exhibition, circa 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Cartoon Art Trust, London (Nov. 19 - Dec. 23), 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - "Celebrating American Drawing: Ashcan to Contemporary," Susan Conway Carroll Gallery (Oct. 17, 1989 - Jan. 1, 1990), 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - City Club of Washington (Nov. 8, 1990) (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Courrier International, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Courrier International, International Press Cartoons Meeting and Exhibition, France, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - "Draw!" National Archives (June 14, 1991 - Aug. 30, 1992), 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Four Seasons Hotel, Inauguration (Jan. 1997), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - French Museum of Contemporary History, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Goethe Institut, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Greater Lafayette Museum of Art, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - The Hague Exhibition (Feb. 2002), 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Loans, 2001; 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Loans, Extensions, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Maryland Art Institute, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Morgan Gallery Exhibition (Jan. 20 - Feb. 24, 1995), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - The Munson Gallery Exhibition, Santa Fe (Apr. 7-21, 1995), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - National Postal Museum (1996-1997), 1994-1998 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - "New Work: Sculpture & Cartoons," Susan Conway Gallery (Dec. 3, 1991 - Jan. 4, 1992), 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 41-42)
    - "Oliphant," Santa Fe Sales (Oct. 14, 2000) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "Oliphant: Ins, Outs and Others 1985-2001," Austalian Embassy (June 7 - July 18, 2001) (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
    - "Oliphant: Ins, Outs and Others 1985-2001," Australian Embassy, Checklist (June 7 - July 18, 2001) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Oliphant: New Directions," Accounting Binder (Mar. 27 - Apr. 28, 1990), 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Oliphant: New Directions," Susan Conway Gallery (Mar. 27 - Apr. 28, 1990) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Oliphant: The New World Order in Drawing and Sculpture" (Box 16)
      - Assembly of Clinton/Gore Sculpture, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Austrian Embassy (Nov. 19 - Dec. 11, 1993), 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
      - Austrian Embassy Exhibition Expenses (Nov. 19 - Dec. 11, 1993), 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Austrian Embassy Opening (Nov. 19 - Dec. 11, 1993), 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Bowdoin College Museum of Art, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Catalog, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
      - Checklist, after 1993, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
      - Condition Book, 1994-1998 (Box 16, Folder 17-18)
      - Condition Report, circa 1994 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Condition Report (Mar. 28, 1996) (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Crate List - Europe, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Domestic Schedule, circa 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Fact Sheet, circa 1993 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Fine Arts Express, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Labels, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - LaGrange College, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - National Gallery of Caricature and Cartoon Art, 1989; 1996 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Publicity, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Rejections, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Slovakia, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
      - Sweet Briar College (Sept. 6 - Oct. 26, 1997), 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - The Trust for Museum Exhibitions, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - USIA, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 34-35)
      - USIA Final, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - USIA and Fine Arts Express, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - USIA Invoices, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - USIA, Stirn Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - "Oliphant: The New World Order in Drawing and Sculpture" (Box 17)
      - USIA Ukraine and Helsinki, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Vienna, Austria, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Words & Pictures Museum, 1993; 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
      - WORLDNET, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Oliphant in Santa Fe," Museum of New Mexico: Museum of Fine Arts (Oct. 13, 2000 - Apr. 8, 2001), 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 6-11)
    - "Oliphant: Three Dimensions," Susan Conway Gallery (Oct. 4-29, 1994) (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Oliphant's Anthem," Library of Congress (Apr. 2 - July 6, 1998) (Box 17)
      - Catalog, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Opening Reception, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
      - Publications, 1990s (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Publicity, 1989; 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
      - Returned Artwork, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Running Account Log, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - "Oliphant's Presidents: 25 Years of Caricature", 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 21-23)
    - "Oliphant's Presidents: 25 Years of Caricature" (Box 17)
      - The Arkansas Arts Center, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Art Services International, 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 25-26)
      - Australia, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Catalog, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Crate List Fact Sheet, circa 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Fullerton Museum Center (Mar. 14 - Apr. 26, 1992) (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - "Oliphant's Presidents: 25 Years of Caricature" (Box 18)
      - Gerald R. Ford Presidential Library and Museum, 1992-1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - National Portrait Gallery, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - National Portrait Gallery (April 1990), 1989-1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - National Portrait Gallery, Gift, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - National Portrait Gallery, Gift Pick-up (Thurs. Nov. 15), 2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - National Portrait Gallery, Photographs (Apr. 6 - Nov. 25, 1990), circa 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - The Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Possible Venues/Declined, circa 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 8-12)
      - Smithsonian PR, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Sweet Briar College (Nov. 13, 1992 - Jan. 3, 1993) (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Tampa Museum of Art, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - "The Other World of Oliphant," Susan Conway Gallery (Mar. 17 - Apr. 25, 1998) (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Pre-Election Exhibition, Susan Conway Gallery (Apr. 4-29, 2000) (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Premio Satira Politca (Forte Dei Marmi, Italy), 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 18-19)
    - Premio Satira Politica (Forte Dei Marmi, Italy), Press, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Premio Satira Politica (Forte Dei Marmi, Italy), Shipping and Packing Lists, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 21-22)
    - "Preview: 1989," Susan Conway Carroll Gallery (Feb. 14 - Apr. 8, 1989) (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Rouen International Press Cartoon Festival Exhibition, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - St. Louis Artists' Guild, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - San Jose State University, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - "Seven Presidents" (Box 18)
      - Albuquerque Museum (July 7 - Aug. 26, 1996), 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 27-28)
      - Australia, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Australia, Peter Cellier, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 30-34)
      - Australian National Maritime Museum, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Bill Clinton Checklist, circa 1990s (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Checklist and Itinerary, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - "Seven Presidents" (Box 19)
      - Condition Book, 1994-2001 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
      - Condition Report and Exhibition Checklist, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - The Contemporary Art Center of Virginia, Kevin Grogan, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - The Cummer Museum of Art (Aug. 27 - Oct. 25, 1998), 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
      - Fact Sheet, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Harry S. Truman Library (May 3 - June 23, 1996) (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - International Museum of Cartoon Art, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Jimmy Carter Library (Feb. 7 - Mar. 29, 1998), 1990-1998 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
        Includes 1 computer disk (3.5")
      - Jimmy Carter Library, Checklist (Feb. 7 - Mar. 29, 1998), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Jimmy Carter Library and CNN (Feb. 7 - Mar. 29, 1998) (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Jimmy Carter Library, Catherine Fox, The Atlanta Constitution (Feb. 7 - Mar. 29, 1998) (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Jimmy Carter Library, Invitations (Feb. 7 - Mar. 29, 1998) (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Loan Forms, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Loan Valuations for Insurance Purposes, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Mississippi Museum of Art (Oct. 14 - Dec. 10, 2000), 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 19-20)
      - Mississippi Museum of Art, Publicity (Oct. 14 - Dec. 10, 2000) (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Museum of Art Fort Lauderdale (Sept. 6 - Nov. 3, 1996), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Museum of Art Fort Lauderdale, Contract (Sept. 6 - Nov. 3, 1996), 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - The Presidential Museum, Odessa, TX (Mar. 3 - Apr. 27, 1996) (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - St. Louis Artists' Guild (Sept. 15 - mid-Nov. 1996), 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - San Diego Museum of Art (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Certificates of Insurance and TCI Shipping Estimates (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995), 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Checklist (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995), 2000 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Condition Book (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995), 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 29-30)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Condition Reports (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Correspondence (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Crate List 1st Shipment (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995), circa 1995 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Examination Prior to Packing (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Extension (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, FAE (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Craig Fuller (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - "Seven Presidents" (Box 20)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Craig Fuller (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Invoices (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Loan Agreement and Budget (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Jane Rice (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995) (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - San Diego Museum of Art, Shipping (Mar. 3 - Dec. 1995), 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Touring Itinerary, circa 1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - University of Colorado at Boulder, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - University of Colorado at Boulder, Loans, 1993-1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Whatcom Museum (Apr. 21 - July 8, 2001) (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Whatcom Museum, Tom Livesay (Apr. 21 - July 8, 2001), 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
      - Whatcom Museum, Publicity (Apr. 21 - July 8, 2001) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Susquehanna Art Museum (Sept. 5 - Nov. 7, 1998) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Tasende Gallery Exhibition (1996), 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Thomas-Nast Society, Landau, Germany (Dec. 6, 1992 - Jan. 31, 1993), 1992-1995 (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
    - Traveling Exhibitions (Box 20)
      - Austria and Eastern Europe, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Bookings, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Expenses, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - FU [Follow-up?], circa 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Mailing Lists, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Notes, circa 2000s (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Prospects, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - The Walters Art Museum, circa 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Woman's National Democratic Club, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Words & Pictures Museum, Loan, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - "The World of Pat Oliphant," Detroit Institute of Arts (Mar. 2 - Apr. 17, 1994), 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 27-30)
    - "The World of Pat Oliphant," Detroit Institute of Arts (Mar. 2 - Apr. 17, 1994) (Box 20)
      - Condition Book, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Condition Report, circa 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Crating and Shipping, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - Invoice, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Restricted Folder (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Press Files, 1976-2003; 4.3
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
    - Clippings [arranged alphabetically by publisher's name], circa 1978-2003 (Box 21, Folder 1-71)
      Includes 1 sound cassette
    - Clippings [arranged alphabetically by publisher's name], 1976-2002 (Box 22, Folder 1-7)
    - Clippings, Commissioned Drawings, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Clippings and Correspondence (Spring), 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, [Photocopies], 1980s-1990s (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, Press Photocopies Set, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Archive [Exhibition Announcements], 1990s (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Magazine Clippings, 1990-2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1980s-2003; 4.4
    - "The Clinton Library" Slides, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Installation Shots of Exhibition at Australian Embassy, circa 1990s-2001 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Portraits of Pat Oliphant, 1980s-1990s (Box 22, Folder 17-18)
    - Rigby, Paul, circa 1990s-2002 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Administrative and Miscellaneous Records, 1978-2003; Series 5; 0.5 Linear feet Box 22
  This series includes records related to the gallery space and daily workings of the gallery, such as flood repairs and permits; samples of contracts; scattered correspondence; a guest book; documents created for Conway’s talks; scattered documentation regarding gifts of artwork; and other miscellaneous records.
  - Artwork Packed and Shipped or Picked-up, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Artwork Pick-up (Nov. 22, 2002), 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Artwork Returned or Called, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Cumberland Island, GA, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Etherington Conservation Center (Box 22)
    - Flood (1999), 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Portfolio Sizes, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Samples, circa 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Flood (August 2001) (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Gallery Contracts, 1980s-1990s (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Glackens House, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Guest Book, ArtChicago, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Home Occupation Permit, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - The Lotos Club, 1988-1991 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - The Mattress Factory, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Mexico, circa 2002 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous [Personal and Gallery Correspondence and Notes], 1993-2002 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - The Phillips Collection, Gifts, 1991-1997 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Pope John Paul II Cultural Foundation, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Property Issues, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Robbins, Warren, National Museum of African Art, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Salon-Saloon, 1981-1988 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Smithsonian Talk Material, 1978; 1996 (Box 22, Folder 41-42)
- Printed Materials, 1987-2002; Series 6; 0.4 Linear feet Box 23, OV 27
  Exhibitions held at the Susan Conway Gallery are documented through exhibition announcements and a handful of catalogs. Also found are some clippings, a brochure, and a catalog for an exhibition at the Library of Congress.
  - Brochure, Washington Art Dealers Association, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, "Celebrity Caricatures" by Wendy Wick Reaves, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, The Phillips Collection Talk, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1999; 2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1987-2002, undated (Box 23, Folder 5-10)
  - Exhibition Announcements, Other Galleries, 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Catalog, "Featuring the Funnies: One Hundred Years of the Comic Strip," Library of Congress, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1987-1990s (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Oversized Exhibition Catalog, "Featuring the Funnies: One Hundred Years of the Comic Strip," Library of Congress, 1995 (Box OV 27)
    Oversized material from Box 23, Folder 12
- Susan Conway Conservation Studio Records, before 1970s-1993; Series 7; 1.2 Linear feet Boxes 23-26
  Records of the Susan Corn Conway Conservation Studio include condition reports, correspondence with clients, notes, and photographs and slides of artwork.
  - American Impressionists Painters, The Phillips Collection, Bill Gerdts (May 1986), circa 1986 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Artists Techniques, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Barnet, Will, Portrait of the Baby Boy of Judge Brine, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Bond, Niles, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Bond, Niles, Collection, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Calfee, William, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Capitol Hill Club, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Carmin, Lewellyn, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Cigna Museum (Philadelphia, PA), 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 22-23)
  - Cigna Museum (Philadelphia, PA), Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Corn, Betty (Mrs. Lovick P.), 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Corn, Elizabeth Turner, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Cote, Charlie, circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1970s-1980s (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Davis, Gene, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Earnshaw, Edward, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Engraving Plate, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Felton, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Friend, Patty, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Grunchec, Philippe, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Haacker, Lee, Dr., 1983; 1990 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Hannaford, Anne, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Herrup, Evelyn, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Horowitz, Peter, Landscape, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Hot Table, circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - House Beautiful, 1983; 1985 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Insurance, Huntington Block Fine Arts Conservators, 1984-1988 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Inventory of American Paintings Before 1914, circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Jekyll Island Club, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Jessup, Wendy, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Kidder, Randolph, Mrs., 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - "Kitchen" (Studio) Remodeling, circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Lecture Presentation, circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Leningrad, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - The Lotos Club, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Maasry, Nadeem George, Ignacio Moreno, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - McAdams, Alfred, Oval Portrait of Young Girl, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Moonshine Mike of Glackens - AKC, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Paper Conservation, circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Pending, 1976-1984 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Pending, O'Connor (Florida), Tolley 4 Paintings, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Piano, 1988; 1985 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Rollins Protective Services, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Rugs, Chinese, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Shelander, Anne, CSRA (Augusta, GA), 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Silk Project, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Slide Presentation, circa 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Studio Clippings, 1972-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Taggart, Jorgensen & Putnam, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Tardio, Robert, Mrs., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Charles S., Mrs., 1986-1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Technique, Special Considerations, 1970s-1980s (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Thistlethwaite, William, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Truland, Mary Woodward, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Tyervar, Franklin, Dr. and Mrs., 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Tyler, William R., Pocohantas by McFarlane, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Capitol, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Vanderpool, Wynant, before 1970s; 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Vieira, Mauro, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Waldron, Bob, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Walsh, James, Dr. and Mrs., 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Watanabe, Dr., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Waters, John, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Wesleyan College, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Wing, Susan, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Wray, Henry, Dr. and Geoffrey Nesbitt, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Yasharoff, Norbert, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Restricted Folder (Box 26, Folder 5)